# **JOHNNY DUNN**

https://github.com/jddunn/ | https://jddunn.github.io/ | johnnyddunn@gmail.com

Remote

### Summary

Full-stack dev experienced in building machine learning infra and data pipelines, training custom models, and fine-tuning LLMs. Experienced in web3 / full-cycle smart contract development, governance / DAOs, MEV bots, and NFT integrations in web and games.

# Professional Experience

**Tilting Point** New York, NY

Senior Blockchain Engineer

Nov 2021 - Feb 2023

- Acted as blockchain architect to build infrastructure and marketplace backend for NFT and token integrations in mobile games publisher SDK on Polygon / MATIC chain, working with MATIC engineers for best practices.
- Developed ERC-20, ERC-721 smart contracts with custom metadata properties, APIs for managing NFT metadata, and internal airdropping service. Architected secure multisig wallet operations; rescued \$1 million+ from missent transactions.

<u>eBay</u> New York, NY

Software Engineer 2 (Full-Stack)

June 2020 - April 2021

- Worked on REST API in Scala & Spring-Boot to service data asynchronously based on item selections to UI, improving UX.
- Created deployment infrastructure process enabling E2E developer experience for backend / ML teams. Set up Jenkins pipelines to connect underlying UI libraries, SSR backends to serve web data, and APIs returning ads data from ML models.

### Freelance (Grapple Media, Notebrush, Edelman, HAL)

NLP Engineer / Software Engineer / Product Designer (Contract)

November 2018 - Jan 2021

- Created user stories, animated wireframes and functional product demo for Notebrush's MVP.
- Developed web crawling infrastructure with automated pipeline to feed data into training news classifiers and sentiment analysis models for Grapple Media.
- Trained models to create photo filters applying aesthetics of specific films to selfies for Edelman's interactive AI exhibits.
- Developed / sold sentiment analysis model to HAL (HereAfterLegacy), and continued development work to deliver their MVP.

#### **IPSoft** New York, NY

Cognitive Implementation Engineer

June 2017 - December 2017

- Implemented modules for virtual assistant AI Amelia for corporate client-facing solutions following agile practices.
- Improved workflow and productivity by writing data processing scripts to be distributed to internal teams.

## **Projects**

Quire.work - Turn static forms and interviews into conversational experiences powered by LLMs. https://quire.work

2023

Restless - Always-on anti-malware software using malicious language processing (HAN model) techniques. https://github.com/jddunn/restless

2020

Text RPG Engine - ES6 JS library to create text adventures / interactive fiction with custom player interactions. https://github.com/iddunn/text-rpg-engine

2020

**Dementia progression analysis** - Dementia progression classifier for MRIs using CNN and transfer learning. https://github.com/jddunn/dementia-progression-analysis

2018

Education

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Design and Technology (May 2017) - Parsons School of Design

### Awards

5<sup>th</sup> Place, AT&T National VR and AR Challenge, with THiNKIMMERSIVE team. (http://npe100.com/)

2017

XRC Labs Young Entrepreneurs Residential Program

Spring 2017

# Skills

<b>Programming Languages</b>	Solidity   Python   Go / Golang   JavaScript   TypeScript   Java   Scala   C#   SQL   HTML   CSS
Frontend	React   Next.js   Redux Toolkit (RTK)   ChakraUI   NextUI   Tailwind   D3.js   three.js   SCSS
Backend	ethers.js   HardHat   LangChain   Hugging Face   OpenAl   FastAPI   Django   Tornado   Keras
	TensorFlow   PyTorch   OpenCV   spaCy   CoreNLP   NumPy   SciPy   pandas   scikit-learn   Celery
	Scrapy   BS4   Selenium   Flashbots   Geth   Gnosis Safe
Databases	MySQL   Postgres   Prisma   SQLAlchemy   MongoDB   GraphQL   Hadoop   Elasticsearch   Redis
DevOps	AWS (EC2, Elastic Beanstalk, Amplify, RedShift)   Docker   Kubernetes   Jenkins
	Unity   Git   Postman   Linux   Burp Suite   Adobe Creative Suite   Processing   openFrameworks
Tools / Software / Other	SketchUp   PyCharm   IntelliJ   Visual Studio   PWAs   Electron   Capacitor   Android Studio